Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Books Illustrated and/or Authored by Leonard Everett Fisher ,undated, 1927-1999
  - The Art of Leonard Everett Fisher
    - "Colonial American Craftsmen" speech, 1972 July 4 (Box 37:1183)
    - Quotes and excerpts from speeches, 1962-1966 (Box 37:1184)
    - "On Tempera" essay, undated (Box 37:1185)
    - "On Drawing" essay, undated (Box 37:1186)
    - "On Preparation, On style and content, On Versatility", undated (Box 37:1187)
    - "Correspondence btwn author and Gerald Johnson", 1960 May 20 (Box 37:1188)
    - Caletto letter, 1965 (Box 37:1189)
    - Connecticut State Legislature statement, 1965 April (Box 37:1190)
    - Material included in book "On Being an Artist", undated (Box 37:1191)
    - "Artist's Choice" essay, 1961 (Box 37:1192)
    - Manuscript 1 of 2, undated (Box 37:1193)
    - Manuscript 2 of 2, undated (Box 37:1194)
  - Journeys [Unpublished]
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 37:1195)
  - Masterpieces of American Painting
    - Notes, undated (Box 37:1196)
    - Description of paintings, undated (Box 37:1197)
    - Manuscript (incomplete), undated (Box 37:1198)
    - Manuscript drafts (incomplete), undated (Box 37:1199)
    - Manuscript, 1984 (Box 37:1200)
  - My Side of the Mountain {Unpublished]
    - Book mock-up, 1975 (Box 37:1201)
  - Stars and Stripes
    - Original Acrylic illustrations (17 items), 1993 (Box 38:1202)
  - Santa Fe Trail
    - Map illustration, undated (Box 38:1203)
  - Aida
    - Acrylic / Gouache illustrations (2 items), 1965 (Box 38:1207)
    - Proof, undated (Box 39:1220)
  - Children's Book Council poster--Acrylic illustration "The Statue of Liberty", 1985 (Box 38:1209)
  - Certificate- belonging to Benjamin Fisher, 1927 (Box 39:1215)
  - Children's Spring Book Festival poster, undated (Box 39:1216)
  - Posters (3 and 1 overlay) of LEF's exhibits, 1968-1970 (Box 39:1217)
  - Posters (2) of LEF's appearances, undated (Box 39:1218)
  - Unidentified proofs (unknown books), undated (Box 40:1219)
  - Alexander
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1221)
  - America, America, America
    - Jacket illustration- pencil and acrylic (rough), undated (Box 40:1222)
  - America is Born
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1223)
  - America Grows Up
    - Jacket covers, undated (Box 40:1124)
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1125)
  - America Moves Forward
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1226)
  - America's Own Mark Twain
    - Proof- jacket cover, undated (Box 40:1227)
  - American Ballads and Songs
    - Illustration sketch, undated (Box 40:1228)
    - Type samples, color samples, undated (Box 40:1229)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 40:1230)
  - The Arabs
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1231)
  - The Archaeology of New York
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 40:1232)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 40:1233)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 40:1234)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 40:1235)
  - Attar of the Ice Valley
    - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 40:1236)
    - Jacket illustration (rough), undated (Box 40:1237)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 40:1238)
  - Balboa
    - Illustration proof, undated (Box 40:1239)
  - Boy Joe Goes to Sea
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 40:1240)
    - Illustration proofs, undated (Box 40:1241)
  - The Burning Jewel
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 40:1242)
    - Illustration proof, undated (Box 40:1243)
    - Uncased proof, 1965 (Box 40:1244)
  - But Not Our Daddy
    - Proofs, 1962 (Box 40:1245)
  - The Coming of the Pilgrims
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1246)
  - Casey at the Bat
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1247)
  - David's Campaign Buttons
    - Pen & Ink illustrations on parchment (16 items), 1959 (Box 40:1248)
    - Jacket illustration proof, undated (Box 40:1249)
  - Danny Kaye's Around the World Story Book
    - Proof, 1960 (Box 40:1250)
  - Declaration of Independence
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1251)
  - Digging into Yesterday
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1252)
  - Dynamite and Peace
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 40:1253)
  - Electromagnetic Waves
    - Proof-jacket, undated (Box 40:1254)
  - Energy and Power
    - Jacket illustrations (2 items), 1957 November (Box 40:1255)
    - Proof- jacket, undated (Box 40:1256)
  - Father Damien and the Bells
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 40:1257)
  - The First Book of Civil War Land Battles
    - Proof- jacket and illustration, undated (Box 40:1258)
    - Gouache illustration, 1960 (Box 46:1421)
  - The First Book of Civil War Naval Actions
    - Jacket illustration- ink & crayon, undated (Box 40:1259)
    - Egg tempera illustration, 1961 (Box 46:1420)
    - Color separations for jacket (oversized), undated (Box 50:1443)
  - The First Book of the Constitution
    - Proof, undated (Box 40:1260)
    - Poster for classroom mobile, undated (Box 40:1261)
    - Jacket cover and page proof, undated (Box 40:1262)
  - Forgotten by Time
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1263)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1264)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1265)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1266)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1267)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1268)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1966 (Box 41:1269)
  - The Golden Child
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1270)
  - The Golden Frog
    - Proofs, undated (Box 41:1271)
  - The Golden Hind
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1272)
  - The Golden Spur
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1963 (Box 41:1273)
    - Original scratchboard illustration, 1963 (Box 41:1274)
  - The Great Archaeologist
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1275)
  - The Great Stone Face
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1276)
  - The Hero in America
    - Illustration notes, 1972 (Box 41:1277)
    - Correspondence, 1972 June 9 (Box 41:1278)
  - The History of the United States 1492-1877
    - Title page, contents, chapter example, 1971 (Box 41:1279)
    - Title sketch, color samples, 1971 (Box 41:1280)
    - Jacket specifications, 1971 (Box 41:1281)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 41:1282)
  - The Horn of Roland
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1283)
  - Indy and Mr. Lincoln
    - Original illustration and color separation, 1960 (Box 41:1284)
    - Illustration from book, 1960 (Box 41:1285)
    - Proof, 1960 (Box 41:1286)
  - JFK's Inaugural Address
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1287)
  - Jo Davidson
    - Proof- illustrations, jundated (Box 41:1288)
  - The Journey of the Gray Whales
    - Jacket sketches on parchment (2 items), undated (Box 41:1289)
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1290)
    - Text-overlay proofs, undated (Box 45:1397)
  - The Joy of Crafts
    - Book notes / plan, 1974 (Box 40:1291)
    - Illustration sketches (11 items), 1974 (Box 41:1292)
    - Scratchboard illustration, 1974 (Box 41:1293)
  - Juan Diego
    - Proof, 1974 (Box 41:1294)
  - Kateri Tekakwitha
    - Proof- jacket, undated (Box 41:1295)
  - Kati and Kormos
    - Proof, undated (Box 41:1296)
  - The Land Beneath the Sea
    - Jacket overlay (plan), undated (Box 42:1297)
    - Notes / illustration plan, undated (Box 42:1298)
    - Color samples, 1970 (Box 42:1299)
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1300)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 42:1301)
  - The Legend of Sleepy Hollow
    - Proof, 1964 (Box 42:1302)
    - Jacket illustration- Gouache, 1965 (Box 46:1419)
  - Let's Find Out About JFK
    - Illustration notes / color examples, undated (Box 42:1303)
    - Proof- jacket, undated (Box 42:1304)
  - Let's Read
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 42:1305)
    - Jacket specifications and color samples, undated (Box 42:1306)
    - Jacket illustration, undated (Box 42:1307)
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 42:1308)
  - Little Calf
    - Jacket flaps, undated (Box 42:1309)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 42:1310)
  - Lora Lorita
    - Proof- jacket, undated (Box 42:1311)
  - Lost By Columbus
    - Jacket illustrations- pen & ink / crayon (5 items), undated (Box 42:1312)
  - The Lost Glacier
    - Jacket illustrations- ink & crayon (2 items), undated (Box 42:1313)
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 42:1314)
  - 
    - Notes, undated (Box 42:1315)
    - Sketch, undated (Box 42:1316)
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1317)
    - Illustration (reproduction), 106- (Box 42:1317A)
  - Macmillan Reading/ Language Arts Anthology
    - Scratchboard illustration "Gregorian Spot", 1991 (Box 42:1318)
    - Scratchboard illustration "Mayan Spot", 1991 (Box 42:1319)
  - Message to Gania
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1320)
  - Mike Fink
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1321)
  - Modern Discoveries in Archeology
    - Proof-illustrations, undated (Box 42:1322)
  - Modern Health
    - Jacket proofs, undated (Box 42:1323)
  - Myers Myers
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1324)
  - My Friends the Huskies
    - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 42:1325)
  - 
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 42:1326)
    - Jacket illustration, undated (Box 42:1327)
    - Scratchboard illustrations (The Night Country) - treated (8), undated (Box 52:1458)
  - Nikola Tesla
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1328)
  - One and One
    - Galley, 1962 September 18 (Box 42:1329)
  - One Small Candle
    - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 42:1330)
    - Jacket illustration, undated (Box 42:1331)
    - Text proof and samples, undated (Box 42:1332)
  - Our Reading Heritage
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 42:1333)
    - Illustration plans, undated (Box 42:1334)
    - Sketches (15), undated (Box 42:1335)
    - Book layouts, undated (Box 42:1336)
    - Table of contents: Book 7 and 8, undated (Box 42:1337)
    - Text dummies, undated (Box 42:1338)
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1339)
  - Paul Bunyan
    - Paul Bunyan, undated (Box 42:1340)
  - Pilgrim Courage
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1341)
  - The Presidency
    - Sketches (14), undated (Box 42:1342)
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 42:1343)
  - Reading Laboratory I
    - Proofs, undated. (Box 42:1344)
  - Reading Laboratory II
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1345)
  - Reading Laboratory III
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1346)
  - The Rib of the Hawk
    - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 42:1347)
    - Jacket illustrations (2), undated (Box 42:1348)
  - Ride Cold Wind
    - Color separations, undated (Box 42:1349)
    - Proof, undated (Box 42:1350)
  - Rip Van Winkle
    - Proof- illustration, undated (Box 42:1351)
  - The Silken Secret
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 43:1352)
    - Jacket illustration sketch- pen & ink, undated (Box 43:1353)
  - Sergeant O'Keefe and his Mule Balaam
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1354)
  - Some Dreams are Nightmares
    - Illustration notes, 1973 (Box 43:1355)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 43:1356)
  - The Splendor of Persia
    - Jacket illustration (rough), undated (Box 43:1357)
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1358)
    - Pen & Ink illustrations for chapter headings, 1957 (Box 50:1447)
  - Sound and Ultrasonics
    - Proofs and jacket cover, undated (Box 43:1359)
  - St. Thomas Aquinas and the Preaching Beggars
    - Proof- cover and illustrations, undated (Box 43:1360)
  - Sybil Ludington (Hartford Group project)
    - Book specifications, undated (Box 43:1361)
    - Original sketches, undated (Box 43:1362)
  - This is the Desert
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1363)
    - Illustration overlays, undated (Box 43:1364)
  - Time
    - Drafts, 1963-1972 (Box 43:1365)
  - To Unknown Lands
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1366)
  - 10,000 Desert Swords
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1367)
  - Verity Mullens and the Indians
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1368)
  - Westward, Westward, Westward
    - Illustration sketches (19), undated (Box 43:1369)
    - Jacket illustration, undated (Box 43:1370)
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1371)
  - Whaling Boy
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1372)
  - Why the Earth Quakes
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1373)
  - William Penn
    - Jacket illustration (Acrylic), August (Box 43:1374)
    - Jacket mock-up, undated (Box 50:1439)
    - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 50:1440)
    - Color separations / jacket proof, undated (Box 50:1441)
  - The World's Most Truthful Man
    - Proof, undated (Box 43:1375)
  - The Year of the Seal
    - Scratchboard illustration (title page), 1970 (Box 43:1376)
    - Scratchboard illustration (p.82), 1970 (Box 43:1377)
    - Scratchboard illustration (p. 112), 1970 (Box 43:1378)
    - Scratchboard illustration (p. 112), 1970 (Box 43:1379)
    - Scratchboard illustration (p.148), 1970 (Box 43:1380)
  - The Year of the Whale
    - Illustration Notes, 1968 (Box 43:1381)
    - Illustrations (4; scratchboard, acrylic, photocopies), 1968 (Box 43:1382)
    - Maps, 1968 (Box 43:1383)
    - Editorial Report, 1968 July 15 (Box 43:1384)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 43:1385)
  - [Unknown Book]
    - Color illustration proofs, undated (Box 45:1398)
  - [Unknown book]
    - Text overlays, undated (Box 45:1399)
  - The British Empire
    - Type mechanical, undated (Box 45:1400)
  - [Unknown book]
    - Galleys (oversized), undated (Box 45:1401)
  - The Burning Mountain
    - Color separations for jacket, undated (Box 45:1402)
  - Napoleon's Marshal
    - Overlays, undated (Box 45:1403)
  - Macmillan / McGraw Hill Reading Book
    - Jacket paste-up, 1993 (Box 45:1404)
  - Around the World Story Book
    - Acrylic illustration, 1960 (Box 46:1405)
    - Acrylic illustration, 1960 (Box 46:1405A)
    - Egg-tempera illustration "Three Aunts", 1960 (Box 46:1405B)
  - Robin Hood
    - Acrylic illustration, 1964 (Box 46:1406)
  - Tales from Shakespeare
    - Acrylic illustration, 1964 (Box 46:1407)
  - The First Book of the War of 1812
    - Acrylic illustration, 1961 (Box 46:1408)
  - The First Book of American Popular Music
    - Scratchboard illustration, 1970 (Box 46:1409)
  - Moby Dick
    - Egg-tempera illustrations (unused), 1956 (Box 46:1410)
  - The Rime of the Ancient Mariner
    - Scratchboard illustrations (3), undated (Box 46:1411)
    - Scratchboard illustrations (2), 1956 (Box 52:1457)
  - Exploits of Xenophon
    - Pencil illustrations, undated (Box 46:1412)
    - Acrylic illustration, undated (Box 46:1413)
  - The Bronze Horse
    - Scratchboard illustration, 1990 (Box 46:1414)
  - Rediscovery of Ancient Egypt
    - Acrylic illustration, 1991 (Box 46:1415)
    - Acrylic illustration, 1991 (Box 46:1416)
  - The Fugitive
    - Scratchboard illustration, 1974 (Box 46:1417)
  - The First Book Edition of the declaration of Independence
    - Egg-tempera illustration, 1960 (Box 46:1418)
  - Painting (framed) of LEF done by Walter Feldman, 1949 (Box 47:1422)
  - Jason and the Golden Fleece
    - F & G, undated (Box 48:1425)
    - Acrylic illustrations (8), 1989 (Box 48:1426)
  - Oversized Mazza Calendar, 1999 (Box 50:1437A)
  - Poster- Youth Theatre "The Shoemaker & the Elves", 1998 (Box 50:1437B)
  - U.S. Postage Stamp Photomechanicals, undated (Box 50:1437C)
  - Exhibit Program cover photomechanicals, c. 1973 (Box 50:1437D)
  - [Unknown book]
    - Overlays, undated (Box 50:1438)
  - Exploring the Great River
    - Proof, undated (Box 50:1442)
  - Illustration (unidentified), undated (Box 50:1444)
  - Pen & Ink drawings- 7 (unidentified), undated (Box 50:1445)
  - Charcoal drawings-5 (unidentified), 1960 (Box 50:1446)
  - Hurray For Books! Streamer and color separations, 1960 (Box 50:1448)
  - Casey at the Bat
    - Scratchboard jacket illustration, 1964 (Box 52:1459)
  - All Times, All People: The World History of Slavery
    - Scratchboard illustrations (8), 1980 (Box 52:1460)
  - Scratchboard illustration- "Gull", 1959 (Box 52:1461)
- Series II: Scrapbooks, Kidstamps and printing blocks,undated
  - Scrapbook of Colonial American Craftsmen books, 1967- (Box 54)
  - Scrapbook of dust jackets from LEF's books, 1961- (Box 55)
  - Dustjackets, stamps designed by LEF, 1975- (Box 56)
  - Dustjackets, 1960- (Box 56)
  - Printing Blocks
    - Brass signature plate, undated (Box 57:2)
    - Brass printing plate for book spine, 1956 (Box 57:3)
    - Copper book plate from To Unknown Lands, undated (Box 57:4)
    - Half-tone printing block, undated (Box 57:5)
    - Half-tone printing block, undated (Box 57:6)
    - Half-tone printing block, undated (Box 57:7)
    - Half-tone printing block, undated (Box 57:8)
    - Half-tone printing block from Lost by Columbus (?), undated (Box 57:9)
    - Half-tone printing blocks (2), undated (Box 57:10)
    - Half-tone printing block, LEF and artwork, undated (Box 57:11)
  - Rubber Kidstamps
    - 2 stamps: Jack in the box and Witch, undated (Box 58:12)
    - Animal stamps: (4) Whale, Whales, Fish, Geese, undated (Box 58:13)
    - Horoscope signs stamps (12), undated (Box 58:14)
    - Illustration plans, undated (Box 58:15)
    - Catalogues and poster for Kidstamps, 1982-1992 (Box 58:16)
- Series III: Filmstrips and Artwork,undated
  - Snow, 1978
    - Scratchboard illustration # 6 / 10, 1978 (Box 59:1)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 7, 1978 (Box 59:2)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 8, 1978 (Box 59:3)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 9, 1978 (Box 59:4)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 11, 1978 (Box 59:5)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 12, 1978 (Box 59:6)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 13, 1978 (Box 59:7)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 14, 1978 (Box 59:8)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 15, 1978 (Box 59:9)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 16, 1978 (Box 59:10)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 17, 1978 (Box 59:11)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 18, 1978 (Box 59:12)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 18, 1978 (Box 59:13)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 20, 1978 (Box 59:14)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 21, 1978 (Box 59:15)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 22, 1978 (Box 59:16)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 23, 1978 (Box 59:17)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 24, 1978 (Box 59:18)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 25, 1978 (Box 59:19)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 26, 1978 (Box 59:20)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 27, 1978 (Box 59:21)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 28, 1978 (Box 59:22)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 29, 1978 (Box 59:23)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 30, 1978 (Box 59:24)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 31, 1978 (Box 59:25)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 32, 1978 (Box 59:26)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 33 / 48, 1978 (Box 59:27)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 34, 1978 (Box 59:28)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 35, 1978 (Box 59:29)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 36, 1978 (Box 59:30)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 37, 1978 (Box 59:31)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 38, 1978 (Box 60:32)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 40, 1978 (Box 60:33)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 41, 1978 (Box 60:34)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 42, 1978 (Box 60:35)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 43, 1978 (Box 60:36)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 44, 1978 (Box 60:37)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 45, 1978 (Box 60:38)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 46, 1978 (Box 60:39)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 47, 1978 (Box 60:40)
  - Judge's House, 1978
    - Scratchboard illustration # 5, 1978 (Box 60:41)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 6, 1978 (Box 60:42)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 8, 1978 (Box 60:43)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 7 / 9, 1978 (Box 60:44)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 11 / 29, 1978 (Box 60:45)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 12 / 48, 1978 (Box 60:46)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 13, 1978 (Box 60:47)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 14, 1978 (Box 60:48)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 15, 1978 (Box 60:49)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 16, 1978 (Box 60:50)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 17, 1978 (Box 60:51)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 18, 1978 (Box 60:52)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 19, 1978 (Box 60:53)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 20, 1978 (Box 60:54)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 21, 1978 (Box 60:55)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 22, 1978 (Box 60:56)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 23, 1978 (Box 60:57)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 24, 1978 (Box 60:58)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 25, 1978 (Box 60:59)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 26, 1978 (Box 60:60)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 27, 1978 (Box 60:61)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 28, 1978 (Box 60:62)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 30, 1978 (Box 60:63)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 31, 1978 (Box 60:64)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 32, 1978 (Box 60:65)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 33, 1978 (Box 60:66)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 34, 1978 (Box 61:67)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 35, 1978 (Box 61:68)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 36, 1978 (Box 61:69)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 37, 1978 (Box 61:70)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 38, 1978 (Box 61:71)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 39, 1978 (Box 61:72)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 40, 1978 (Box 61:73)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 41, 1978 (Box 61:74)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 42, 1978 (Box 61:75)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 43, 1978 (Box 61:76)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 45, 1978 (Box 61:77)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 46, 1978 (Box 61:78)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 47, 1978 (Box 61:79)
    - Scratchboard illustration # 49, 1978 (Box 61:80)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, 1978
    - Scratchboard illustration #6, 1978 (Box 61:81)
    - Scratchboard illustration #7, 1978 (Box 61:82)
    - Scratchboard illustration #8, 1978 (Box 61:83)
    - Scratchboard illustration #9, 1978 (Box 61:84)
    - Scratchboard illustration #10, 1978 (Box 61:85)
    - Scratchboard illustration #11, 1978 (Box 61:86)
    - Scratchboard illustration #13, 1978 (Box 61:87)
    - Scratchboard illustration #14, 1978 (Box 61:88)
    - Scratchboard illustration #15, 1978 (Box 61:89)
    - Scratchboard illustration #16, 1978 (Box 61:90)
    - Scratchboard illustration #17, 1978 (Box 61:91)
    - Scratchboard illustration #18, 1978 (Box 61:92)
    - Scratchboard illustration #19 / 49, 1978 (Box 61:93)
    - Scratchboard illustration #20, 1978 (Box 61:94)
    - Scratchboard illustration #21, 1978 (Box 61:95)
    - Scratchboard illustration #22, 1978 (Box 61:96)
    - Scratchboard illustration #23, 1978 (Box 61:97)
    - Scratchboard illustration #24, 1978 (Box 61:98)
    - Scratchboard illustration #25, 1978 (Box 62:99)
    - Scratchboard illustration #25, 1978 (Box 62:100)
    - Scratchboard illustration #27, 1978 (Box 62:101)
    - Scratchboard illustration #28, 1978 (Box 62:102)
    - Scratchboard illustration #29, 1978 (Box 62:103)
    - Scratchboard illustration #30, 1978 (Box 62:104)
    - Scratchboard illustration #31, 1978 (Box 62:105)
    - Scratchboard illustration #32, 1978 (Box 62:106)
    - Scratchboard illustration #34, 1978 (Box 62:107)
    - Scratchboard illustration #35, 1978 (Box 62:108)
    - Scratchboard illustration #36 / 49, 1978 (Box 62:109)
    - Scratchboard illustration #37, 1978 (Box 62:110)
    - Scratchboard illustration #38, 1978 (Box 62:111)
    - Scratchboard illustration #39, 1978 (Box 62:112)
    - Scratchboard illustration #40, 1978 (Box 62:113)
    - Scratchboard illustration #41, 1978 (Box 62:114)
    - Scratchboard illustration #42, 1978 (Box 62:115)
    - Scratchboard illustration #43, 1978 (Box 62:116)
    - Scratchboard illustration #44, 1978 (Box 62:117)
    - Scratchboard illustration #46, 1978 (Box 62:118)
    - Scratchboard illustration #47, 1978 (Box 62:119)
    - Scratchboard illustration #48 / 49, 1978 (Box 62:120)
    - Scratchboard illustration #50, 1978 (Box 62:121)
    - Scratchboard illustration #51, 1978 (Box 62:122)
    - Scratchboard illustration #52, 1978 (Box 62:123)
    - Scratchboard illustration #56, 1978 (Box 62:124)
    - Scratchboard illustration #58, 1978 (Box 62:125)
  - The Tenant, undated
    - Script (19 pages), undated (Box 63:126)
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 63:127)